Training to strengthen the new center
In order to strengthen Inoue, the 4th center, we first delved deeper into him with a personal quiz, and won 10,000 yen in prize money.
Ladies and gentlemen, please, let's have a quiz!
Ahhhhh!
This time, we'll be quizzing Inoue on the experiences of the past senior directors, and Inoue will be asked to learn their secrets.
I'd like to get paid for this.
I'd like to get some money from you.
The problem of filling in the holes.
Oh, yes!
What is it that you do just before you sing a song at a live performance?
It's difficult.
It's difficult
Is the length of the song a clue?
Yes, it's not just one letter.
Oh, yes.
I can't do it anymore.
I don't know.
Let's see...
Let's see.
Inoue, please answer.
Timing.
I wonder if you're right about the timing, Mr. Himuro.
Sad.
He's so cute.
Too bad.
It's hard to tell.
The correct answer was tension.
Tension
I don't know what this means, Kubo, but it depends on the scene of the live performance, the tone of the song, and the title of the song.
I was "Hito wa Yume twice" (People will see your dreams twice), so please listen to it quietly.
That's right.
And the MC block.
Also, I heard that you can't bite your tongue.
I was watching it, but it's possible that I bit a lot, and that makes me nervous.
I'm very nervous, and I tend to play more quiet songs, but Kakihara-chan seems to think I'm a pro at this kind of tension.
I tend to play more upbeat songs, so please listen to this one.
I want the audience to get excited from this point on, so I'm going to raise the tension in a fun and cheerful way and then let out a yell when I get to the point where I want the song to start.
I'm going to raise the tension and make the audience happy and cheerful, and then I'm going to raise it a little bit before the song.
I've just learned two things, what I've just learned and what you just said, and I need to spend a little more time here thinking about it.
I need to spend a little more time thinking about this.
I'm not sure if it's a long one or a hard one, but it's a hard place to get to.
I don't want to be a pom-pom, either.
It's a lot of fun...
I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm fine...
I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm fine. Icy? Okay, well, I guess we're going to go now.
Okay, we're going to the last block.
Are you guys ready for some fun?
Yeah!
Let's go to the next song.
Listen to this one, Icey.
Oh, is that it?
This much?
I know you're probably really embarrassed right now because you haven't done any live shows.
It's okay. It's okay.
It was a lot of fun.
So, why don't we practice with the Icy now?
Because there's a chance we might do it.
What? Can I say "you guys"?
I don't care if it's you guys.
I don't care if it's you guys. I don't care if it's you guys. Let's give it a try.
I'll go.
Pretend you're holding a microphone.
Good luck.
Okay, let's go.
Are you guys ready to get excited?
No, I'm not!
Are you ready to get excited?
Yes!
Now please listen to the following
IC
Oh, it's good, it's good, it's good.
It's so good!
It's good, it's good, it's good, it's good.
I have a point to make.
Everyone was looking at Inoue at the time, so I wish they'd show their faces or something.
You guys?
You guys!
Your hair is long, too.
You want to see his face.
There's no way we'll get a kid with moist hair.
You're right.
What are we going to do about the moist ones?
I've got to take a break from my work... and I'll finish up with the next song.
Listen... they say one should dream twice.
That's not true at all
This next song will be our last song.
Please listen to the next song.
People dream twice
Yes, yes, yes.
Is this one good?
Yes, it's basically great, but...
But before I say the name of the song, let's change the atmosphere for a moment.
I know what you mean.
I get it. I get it.
How do you change it there?
And then, listen to me. People dream twice.
Let's get started. The next song will be the last song.
Now listen to this. People will dream twice.
I don't know... it didn't feel any different after that pause.
I didn't feel any different. It didn't feel different? More like...
Should I think about people dreaming twice? Yes.
It's good to do it that way. It depends on whether you put emotion into it or not.
It makes a big difference.
It's like a workshop.
This is...
It's an intensive course on relationships.
People dream twice... so let's say you feel it.
Let's give it a shot.
Okay, let's go. Let's go for it. Start.
The next song will be the last song.
Please listen to it.
People dream twice
That's great!
Okay, let's go to the next one, Yoda.
Yoda, maybe there is a Yoda.
But I...
It's my first time to be in the center.
Runaway Water.
I was double-centered with Momoko Oizono.
There was a version called "Oizono's version" and I wondered what the version of the throne was...
Okay, I'll take it... then let's reminisce about those days.
Now please listen to this booby prize.
I'm nervous like this, so my intonation is going in that direction.
That's right.
Okay, you can go ahead and do it.
Okay, let's start.
Okay, please listen.
Running away mistake.
That's...
That's funny.
That's what he said.
That's why I'm telling you.
Nagi, you're so amazing, I've never seen anything like it.
I've never seen you do it so openly.
I've never seen you do it.
It's all right, because she was like that before, and she's doing it now.
We couldn't do it like that.
Really?
We spent so much time on the first question.
That was a lot of practice.
Thank you.
Let's continue with the next question.
What made Mizuki Yamashita happiest when she became the center?
Number 1, the center looks thinner.
Number 2, being congratulated in other shows.
No. 3, getting hooked on Mr. Tamori. Armstay No. 4, swinging is easy.
I was able to play the center role in a regulation song once, but I was wondering if it would be Nikkasan, but I often see Yamashita-san in other shows, so...
What should I do?
I'm number 3.
I'm into Tamori-san.
What do you think, Mr. Himura?
Too bad.
Yamashita...
The first one.
I was happy to see that the middle one looks thinner.
Eh?
The one on the edge is a bit of an observer's view.
Oh, that kind of thing.
But this other stuff was also said by people who've been to the center in the past.
I see.
Number 2 is Kubo.
She was in the center during the drama filming period.
People who heard about it on the news said, "Shio-chan's at the center.
"Shio-chan's at the center!
Tiger, right?
That's right.
They celebrated at a great place.
That's great.
I'm so happy for you.
Number 3, this is Yoda.
It's not that I got hooked on him or anything, but he happened to have a key chain from Kagoshima, my hometown.
After the show, I was so happy to see him wearing it on his cell phone strap in the dressing room and telling me how great I looked in such a short time.
I told him that I like to put the "Deer Island" in the bathtub with the hot spring water, and Tamori-san said, "That's nice!
I was so happy that Tamori-san said, "That's nice, isn't it?
I was happy that Tamori-san said it was a good idea.
The center of the stage is the biggest part of the center.
a...from the 50th number to the 2nd number...it's totally possible...it's super hard...it's totally possible...everyone's laughing about it...but...what number is it now?
What's the number now?
Are you doing it? Are you watching?
Are you watching?
But if, for example, a different girl makes a mistake...
What? Isn't this the wrong place for me? And then, all of a sudden...
Then all of a sudden, it falls apart.
Yes, yes, yes.
I used to think I was in the right place.
I was dancing with a big smile on my face.
I thought I was in the right position, but it turned out to be Yoda's position.
Yumeki was wrong?
I made a mistake, but Yoda-san tried his best to get into my position.
But I didn't move out of the way.
So there was no room for him.
Then, from the customer's point of view, it looked like Yoda was wrong.
But I don't have absolute confidence either, so it's like I'm wrong about everything.
I see... this is tough.
Well then, let's continue.
Kaka Kakihara
As the center, what do you think you should pay attention to before shooting a music video?
Before a music video?
I'm bursting out laughing here.
Don't be too round.
What's this?
It's too long!
I don't know what it is, but I'm going to ask you to fill in the blanks and try not to cut your bangs too much.
How about now?
This is famous... we did it on this show... but did you know... this is when you scolded me...
This is when you scolded me.
I went to a salon I don't usually go to because I wanted to get into shape.
It was my first time.
That's dangerous.
I went to a hair salon I'm used to wearing.
Wear shoes you're used to.
I see.
After all, when you're at the center for the first time...
I wasn't used to Tokyo.
I went to a hair salon in Omotesando.
But everyone in Omotesando in Tokyo is good at what they do, so don't worry.
I told them to keep my bangs below my eyebrows.
I said.
I said, "Okay.
I said, "Okay," and left it to him.
I said "poof" and her eyebrows went up.
I didn't say that, but I already cut it off.
I thought I cut it off, but I couldn't say it, so I got shampooed while crying.
I got shampooed while crying
Why are you crying while getting shampooed?
They say, "Why are you crying?
It's your fault.
I couldn't say anything, so I cut it off.
I put a lot of hair-growth tonic on it.
Hair growth tonic doesn't grow in a day.
It didn't grow.
You got it to grow back really well on the job site.
It did on site, too.
I had to crush it to make it last a little longer.
He doesn't want his idol to do the same thing... except more differently... because he has a habit of cutting his hair.
Hmmm...
What did we inadvertently do when we decided to do a post with Kashoudamori-san for the new center project on the show?
Yes, here it is. Only then we did a honyarara.
Many of the members who did this have since graduated.
That's right.
This was for when Asuka went to M-Start,
Then, let's do it for practice, and we did it here.
Yes, I did it.
I said, "Yes," and we did it.
I don't know if you can understand. I mean this. Only at that time, it was easy.
It was difficult or something, right?
I wonder if it adds up.
For example, if I said, "Let's try m-stepping now," and the members were like, "Okay, let's go, 321," everyone would straighten their backs.
I'm not sure why you didn't do it properly, but you were in there, Mr. Mori, so I understand that, I do.
I'll go.
Okay, let's go.
And now, for the first time in a while... we continue with Nogizaka46.
This is the 33rd one?
Yes, sir.
Yes. What's the name?
I'm Nagi Inoue, from Nogizaka46.
Inoue?
Nagi.
Nagi?
Yes, sir.
What kind of a husband is this this time?
Okay, let's go.
The second challenge of Himstay!
And now, Nogizaka-bochin 6 years old.
Yes, please. It's been a while, right?
Yes, it's been a while since you've been in the center of the 33rd album, hasn't it? That's right.
So, you are the 33rd one, and you are the center?
Yes, please.
Which name?
It's Nagi Inoue from Nogizaka46.
Inoue?
Yes, I'm Nagi.
I am Nagi.
Nagi? That's unusual. Is that your real name?
It is my real name. People often say it is unusual.
I see.
Okay, let's see what you have to say.
I have at least one question.
I'm sure you're right, it would be nice if I could say something about what I heard yesterday.
I wish I could tell you what I heard yesterday.
My father often wears sunglasses.
That's nice.
So, Mr. Tamori...
Let's do it once.
Next is Nogizaka46
Good morning.
It's hot, isn't it?
Yes, it is
What's your name?
I'm Inoue Nagi from Nogizaka46 Nagi Inoue Nagi, what's your name? Nagi Inoue, from Nagizaka46
Inoue?
Nagi.
Nagi? It's a difficult name.
It's "Nagi" written "wa" for Japanese confectionery.
It's a beautiful name.
I see.
My father often wears sunglasses.
Okay, let's listen to the song.
There's been an accident.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'd better not tell you. If I tell you now, you'll probably cry when I sing.
I'm not going to do that. And don't miss it, Mr. Tamura, he's going to come in with that volume.
And don't miss it, Tamura-san, because you're coming in with such a loud voice.
I'm going to come in a little too loud.
I'll come just like that...
Oh, yes...
It's a little too much for you...
I'm making it worse for Mr. Mori
You're making it worse for Mr. Mori
Next episode's preview
What was the hardest thing for the 4th generation Yuki when he was the center?
4 choices!
No.1, dancing at the front of the line.
No.2, that there were few motives
No.3 sea turtle search hit feeling
No.4 Comment on all the performances during the tour No.3 Praying for a hit in search of sea turtles
No.4 comment of all performances during the tour
I don't know. Well, I'm going to split them all, but it's hard to decide between one or four.
I'm on tour now, and I'm not sure if I'm going to make a comment or not, so I'm afraid to dance in front of the audience.
I'm afraid to dance at the front of the line.
I've decided.
Which one?
To dance at the very front of the line
To dance at the very front
What do you think, Mr. Himuro?
What do you think, Himuro-san?
Just now, Tamura-san.
Tamura-san.
Tamura-san, right?
Too bad, too bad... It was my first time to pray for a hit at the center, so I was under a lot of pressure to make it a success, and there were no turtles in the sea, so I couldn't find any.
I couldn't find any turtles... I had Kaloki, too, so it would have been really bad if I couldn't find any, and I also had to get certified, and that's where I started learning about life clubs, so it took me quite a few days to get certified.
That's right.
After the dive, I had to go to a training session.
I was exhausted.
You didn't have much incentive.
This was back then.
The seniors were like monsters.
They have an amazing aura about them.
I kept saying Momochan.
"Why Momoko and the others?
I kept saying to Momochan, "I wonder why we're here... why we're here... why we're here...
Then please listen. Don't look.
I was so anxious... but now that I've heard this, I wish I'd gone to my seniors and asked them to tell me.
I thought it was important to get over it alone at that time.
I know it's not that I don't know what to do and when to ask, and I know you're always welcome to come to me, but I do understand how you feel.
I understand how you feel, so it would be nice if we could tell you. The next question is the last one, but it's the last one, and it's not right.
I didn't get it right. No, you didn't.
All the past centers...
What do all the past centers think about Inoue this time?
What?
You took a survey about that?
Here we go.
I want you to stay.
Yes, I do. I want you to be there.
Well, you know, it's the center.
I don't want you to go away.
What, you want me to stay? That's what you mean.
Come on.
Let's go. Decide. Go ahead.
I want you to smile.
That's a very nice answer.
What do you say, gentlemen?
Yes, sir.
I want you to keep smiling.
I'm sorry.
Shame.
Shame. - Shame.
The correct answer is, I want you to stay healthy.
Well, Kubo.
I don't often get sick myself.
But I got sick for the first time during the Center.
Anyway, I want you to eat well and sleep well.
I want you to stay healthy.
I see.
I see. Health comes first.
This is Yodamo.
Yes, that's right. I would be very worried if he was too preoccupied and couldn't eat, so I would like him to be healthy and active.
That's great. Everyone has that in common.
And persimmons. I think Nagi-chan can think about other people and see what's going on around her, and that's why she's always thinking about the people around her.
I think that's why she feels like she has to work harder than anyone else, and that's why she feels ill from her feelings the most.
So don't cry.
Keep smiling.
That's right.
I know I'm not here today, but...
Endo and Yamashita too.
That's right.
I've never been to a center before.
I still want you to be healthy.
I think everyone thinks so.
And from Yamashita.
Let's be careful with the flirtatious speech.
What? Why?
Nori gets in my teeth and I have to drink it.
Meki and the others have said it too, but the Nori dialect really gets into you... so many Nori-ben lately... so many Nori-ben, but it's still popular... so it's not so bad...
The past center members have become a bit healthier.
What?
The quiz was a bit disappointing.
Saito Asuka's graduation concert
Blu-ray & DVD jacket photos are ready!
Tickets for UnderLive streaming are now on sale!
Ah!
Hello everyone, this is Mizuki Yamashita, how are you? If you didn't subscribe to my channel, I'm going to pico-pico-pico you.
Pico, pico, pico, pico, pico!
Bye bye!